# Arjun Krishna Software Engineer Adobe

Mobile: +918848661970

Website: <a href="https://arjunkrishnak.github.io/">https://arjunkrishnak.github.io/</a> Email: <a href="mailto:arjunkrishna.office@gmail.com">arjunkrishna.office@gmail.com</a>

LinkedIn: <a href="https://github.com/in/arjun-krishna-k">www.linkedin.com/in/arjun-krishna-k</a> GitHub: <a href="https://github.com/ArjunKrishnak">https://github.com/ArjunKrishnak</a>

## **Summary:**

Through my projects and work experience, I was able to familiarize myself how to handle big data, develop POCs around machine learning models and develop machine learning solutions in production. I am also familiar with SOLID design principles, data structures, system design and test-driven development to provide end to end solutions. I would love to work with companies working on challenging products and ideas

## **Education:**

Year	Degree	Institution	Percentage
2015-2019	B. Tech. Electronics Major, Computer science Minor	IIT Roorkee	93.86%
2013-2015	Senior high school (11 <sup>th</sup> and 12 <sup>th</sup> Grade)	Bharatiya Vidya Bhavan	97%
2012-2013	High school (10 <sup>th</sup> Grade)	Bharatiya Vidya Bhavan	100%

# Experience:

Duration	Role	Institution	Description
Jun 2019 – Present	Software Developer	Adobe Systems	Developed Genshop which is Adobe's inhouse deep learning python library for Generative models primarily GANs. Worked on CPU (single and multithreaded) and GPU workflows of Adobe Color Engine (ACE) and Modular Parsing System (MPS)
May 2018 - July 2018 (3 months)	Research Intern	Adobe Systems	Interned with Big Data Experience Lab, Adobe Research, Bengaluru on the project personalized highlighting based on reader feedback.
Dec 2017 – Jan 2018(2 months)	Research Assistant	IIT Roorkee	Worked on Action Recognition with feature fusion which involved combining traditional computer vision techniques with deep learning to improve the accuracy of Action Recognition.

## Certifications:

Title	Institution	Platform	Percentage
Machine Learning	Stanford	Coursera	97.6%
Applied AI with Deep Learning	IBM	Coursera	99.2%

Fundamentals of Scalable Data Science	IBM	Coursera	97.7%
Advanced Machine Learning and Signal Processing	IBM	Coursera	97.7%

#### Skills:

- Programming: C++, Python, Java, JavaScript C, Objective C, MATLAB
- Databases: SQL, MongoDb, Apache RDD, Indexed DB
- Frameworks: Pytorch, TensorFlow, SparkML, React.js, Node.js, Flask, Android SDK, DirectX12, Metal, Microsoft SDK, Emscripten
- Developer tools: Git, Perforce, Visual Studio, Android Studio, XCode, PyCharm
- Consoles: Linux, AWS, Windows, Mac

#### **Projects:**

Title	Description	Technology stack
Express Wiki	A website that gives you a personal online Wikipedia powered by AI so you can read and organize your Wikipedia.	React, MongoDB, NodeJS, JavaScript, AWS, Python
Intelligent Font Search	Developed POC which applies combination of NLP and Deep Learning to facilitate natural language complex query for font search.	Python, Pytorch, React, Flask, AWS
Video segment copy detection	In this B. Tech. thesis work of mine, I have tried to introduce a video hashing method for scalable video segment copy detection to prevent proliferation of toxic and illegal copies of videos online.	Python, Pytorch, Flask

For more of my work and open source contributions please head over to my website

## Achievements:

- Best B.Tech. Project Award received from director IIT Roorkee amongst 1816 students.
- Winner Adobe Shark Tank event amongst 100+ new hires.
- KVPY National Scholarship 2015 Fellow ~1,50,000 high school candidates.
- Cleared First Stage of CODEFUNDO 2015 conducted by Microsoft.
- District topper of AISSCE (All India Senior School Certificate Examination) 2015 certificate received from education minister India.

## Domain Knowledge:

Data analysis, Machine Learning, Storage Scalability, System Design, Web Development, Computer Vision, Natural Language Processing, Android App Development, Image processing

## References:

Saikat Chakrabarthy	Vinod Pankajakshan
Computer Scientist 2	Assistant Professor
Adobe Systems	Electronics Department, IIT Roorkee
chakraba@adobe.com	vinodfec@iitr.ac.in